import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Урок от 6го марта',
  cards: [{
    question: 'ones',
    answer: 'клетка в биологическом смысле',
  }, {
    question: 'nearly',
    answer: 'почти',
  },{
    question: 'fungi',
    answer: 'грибки',
  },{
    question: 'digestive system',
    answer: 'пищеварительная система',
  },{
    question: 'disease',
    answer: 'заболевание',
  },{
    question: 'illness',
    answer: 'заболевание',
  },{
    question: 'harmful',
    answer: 'вредный',
  },{
    question: 'essential',
    answer: 'жизненеобходимый',
  },{
    question: 'gut',
    answer: 'кишечник',
  },{
    question: 'to suggest',
    answer: 'предполагать',
  },{
    question: 'in front of',
    answer: 'напротив',
  },],
} as Category;
